Guide to the Henry S. Huntington Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Henry S. Huntington Family Papers
1805-1949
RG 109
Yale University Divinity School Library
30
(61 boxes)
Correspondence, writings, and collected material in the Henry S. Huntington Family Papers provide documentaton of an educated clergy family's life in New England, particularly during the Victorian era. Henry Strong Huntington (1836-1920) was a Congregational minister in New Hampshire, Illinois, Maine, and Massachusetts. Three of his children were involved with mission work in Turkey.
Huntington, Henry Strong, 1836-1920
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Anna H. Deming.
Biographical / Historical
1836Jul Henry Strong Huntington born in New York, NY son of Oliver Ellsworth Huntington and Mary Ann Strong
1840 Nov Mary Ann Strong Huntington (HSH's mother) died.
1841Apr Mary Lawrence Herbert born in Ellsworth, ME, daughter of George and Theresa Arms
1854 Apr Oliver Ellsworth Huntington married Eunice Kimberly Hitchcock (b. 1825 Aug 19)
1857 HSH graduated from Yale College
1862 HSH graduated from Andover Theological Seminary
1863-1872 HSH was minister at the Congregational Church in Warner, NH
1870 Dec HSH and MLH married
1872-1876 HSH was minister at the First Church of Galesburg, IL
1872Oct Cornelia Strong Huntington born. Graduated from Wellesley College, 189[6?]. Married Theron J. Damon on July 20, 1911.
1875May Theresa Lyman Huntington born. Married Charles Lincoln Zeigler on Oct 18, 1906.
1876 Sep Ellsworth Huntington born. Graduated from Beloit College, 1897. Teacher at Euphrates College in Harpoot, Turkey, 1898-1902[?]. MA, Harvard University, 1902. Ph.D., Yale University, 1909. He married Rachel Slocum Brewer on Dec 22, 1917. For a detailed account of his early career, see his entry in the Huntington Family Genealogy (Box 49, Folder 605) See also his papers at Sterling Memorial Library Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University.
1877-1887 HSH was minister at the Congregational Church in Gorham, ME
1877 Jul Oliver Ellsworth Huntington (HSH's father) died.
1878 Apr George Herbert Huntington born. Graduated from Williams College, 1900. Teacher at Robert College, Constantinople, until 1904. B.D., Hartford Theological Seminary, 1907. Ordained a Congregational minister in Milton, MA in 1907. He then returned to Robert College as Principal. Married Elizabeth W. Dodge in 191[6?].
1881 Feb Henry Strong Huntington, Jr. born. Graduated from Yale College, 1904. B.D. Auburn Theological Seminary, 1911. Ordained in Milton, MA, 1911. Married Edith Marguerita Foster on Dec 26, 1912.
1882 Oct George Herbert (MLH's father) died.
1882 Nov Ruth Lawrence Huntington born. Graduated from Wellesley College. Married Samuel Adams Fletcher on Jun 5, 1906.
1888-1907 HSH was minister at the Congregational Church in Milton, MA. Thereafter, he was pastor emeritus of the Milton church.
1890 Theresa (Arms) Herbert (MLH's mother) died.
1910 Mar Eunice (Hitchcock) Huntington (HSH's step-mother) died.
1920 HSH died.
192[4?] MLH died.
Scope and Contents
Henry S. Huntington and his family corresponded frequently, wrote extensively, and saved material comprehensively. The extent and detail of the documentation available in this record group provide valuable insight into the life and times of a New England Congregational clergyman and his family from the 1870s through the early part of this century. This record group is complemented by the papers of Yale professor and geographer Ellsworth Huntington, son of Henry and Mary, which are held at Sterling Memorial Library.
Of particular interest in relation to other Divinity Library holdings is documentation pertaining to mission work in Turkey. Mary Lawrence (Herbert) Peabody, Mary Huntington's aunt, was a missionary to Turkey (Erzoom) in the mid-nineteenth century, serving under the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions. Four of the six Huntington children spent significant periods of time in Turkey as missionaries or teachers. Theresa Huntington served as an American Board missionary to Harpoot from 1898 to 1906. George Huntington moved to Constantinople to teach at Robert College after his graduation from Williams College. He returned to the U.S. to obtain a B.D. in 1907 and then returned to Robert College. Cornelia Huntington seems to have traveled to Turkey to join her brother and live there. It is not clear if she did mission work or was a teacher, but she lived with George at Robert College for a number of years until she met journalist Theron J. Damon, whom she eventually married. The Damons made their home in Constantinople for a number of years, sharing a joint household with George and Elizabeth Huntington for a period before moving back to the U. S. around 1921. Ellsworth Huntington taught at Euphrates College in Harpoot, Turkey, for a few years beginning in 1898 and traveled in the area later in his career. Henry and Mary Huntington visited their children in Turkey and corresponded with various individuals involved in Turkish missions.
The Family Correspondence of Series I includes correspondence of four generations of the nuclear Huntington family, as well as letters to and from the extended Huntington clan. A listing of names and nicknames that will assist in deciphering family relationships is contained in the first folder of this series. Various events can be traced through the family correspondence. Letters from Mary to Henry in 1872, for example, give information about a major fire and its aftermath in Chicago, where Mary's parents were living. Detailed letters written from Turkey provide substantial information about the life and work of the Huntington children there.
The General Correspondence of Series II is arranged in two parts: letters to and from Henry S. Huntington and letters to and from Mary Lawrence (Herbert) Huntington. The few letters written by HSH and MLH tend to be rough drafts, kept as a record of communications sent. The vast majority of the correspondence is letters written to HSH and MLH by friends, church members, and other individuals. A small amount of general correspondence to and from the children and parents of HSH and MLH has been placed in Series I, as its interest lies primarily in its relation to family matters.
Of particular interest in the General Correspondence series are letters from J. R. Sculpham, a classmate of Mary's who served in the Civil War, and the correspondence of F. C. Jones to HSH. Jones and Huntington were classmates at Yale and kept in close contact throughout their adult lives. The two frequently exchanged sermon topics and reviewed books for each other. One letter of substantial content is Jones' June 22, 1907 letter to his Yale classmates for their 50th reunion in which he affectionately recalls his time at Yale. Also of note are the numerous missionary letters received and saved by the Huntingtons, including from missionaries J. Browne, C. Gates, George Knapp, Helen and Mary Barnum, Caroline Bush, Annie Gordon, Mary Kinney, and Anna Knapp in Turkey, Henry Bruce in India, S. F. Woodin in Foochow, China. and Sila C. Winn in Yokohama, Japan.
The correspondence of Henry Huntington reveals his interest in a variety of topics. HSH apparently solicited accounts of various religious revivals in New England from area ministers in 1870. Descriptive accounts are contained in letters from Jacob Chapman of Deerfield NH, E. M. Kellogg [of Lynn, MA?], Silas Ketchum of Bristol NH, L. P. Leeds of Hanover, NH (Dartmouth College Church), and William S. Savage of Franklin, CT. HSH was concerned with the morality of "Moving Picture Shows." He offered a resolution at a Springfield conference in May 19, 1910 asking the Committee on Moral Issues to investigate the morality of the "amusements" and the "duty of the churches in reference to it" and to report back in 1911. There were also several clippings saved concerning the content of theater and cinema entertainment, which can be found in the collected material. See also a letter to HSH from George B. Ward, President of the Board of Commissioners, City of Birmingham, March 22, 1917.
The Writings of Series III include sermon manuscripts and sermon notes of HSH, articles, notebooks, and journals. Notebooks kept by HSH contain lecture notes from Yale College and Andover Theological Seminary, notes from various meetings, especially Boston Ministers' Meetings, and other conferences or occasional lectures. HSH's early habit of writing detailed accounts of his days ceased as he got older. MLH used her notebooks for appointment and record keeping, or for notes at meetings.
HSH wrote an extensive manuscript on the life of Samuel Huntington, which he attempted to get published. Samuel Huntington was a legislator for the state of Connecticut shortly after the Revolutionary War; HSH's great-great-great-great-great grandfather was Samuel Huntington's great-great grandfather. While there is no evidence of actual publication of the manuscript, several drafts are in the collection, accompanied by a great deal of supporting material relating to his research, writing, and publishing efforts. HSH kept the notes he made on various books about New England and American history in labeled envelopes. The notes and the envelopes had deteriorated significantly, and the notes consisted primarily of page references, so a small sample was photocopied (especially the labels from the envelopes) and the remainder discarded. One packet was kept intact because it appeared to be a more complete synthesis of HSH's research on the Puritans and early New England. It may be that he was intending to write a second manuscript after his research on Samuel Huntington was complete.
The Huntington family of Norwich, CT was a vast web of individuals and families who traced their ancestry back to one Simon Huntington. The Huntington Family in America (Hartford: Huntington Family Association, 1915), which is available at Sterling Memorial Library, provides extensive genealogical information. The Huntingtons' interest in documenting family events and history is reflected in Series IV, Biographical Documentation. The series includes datebooks and journals, account/record books, financial records, printed material, and photographs.
The account books provide an interesting log of various financial matters, as well as other records. MLH frequently kept written records of how many letters she had written and to whom. Records were kept of cash on hand, Christmas gifts given and received, and purchases. One book of church records includes all the baptisms, marriages, funerals performed by HSH, and an alphabetical record of weekly church attendance from 1872-1876 in Galesburg, IL.
The collected material of Series V covers a wide range of types of material, the bulk of it revealing Victorian style. The Huntington were inveterate collectors and not all the material they collected has been retained. For example, the Huntingtons clipped hundreds of newspaper articles and saved them in bunches and bags. The clippings ranged from missionary accounts and war news from Turkey to the daily columns of particular journalists as well as diet tips and advice for how to raise children. All of the clippings relating to missionary work or other topics regarding Christianity and Congregationalism were saved. An attempt was made to divide the collected printed material topically. Samples of the more mundane clippings were also saved, to give an idea of the type of material they found interesting. Of particular cultural interest may be the advertisements and catalogues that the Huntingtons saved, which reveal the materialism of the day and major concerns for household living. But most of these clippings were from major Boston newspapers, such as the Boston Herald and the Tribune, and thus can be found at many other libraries. To save space, we discarded a large number of them.
The Huntingtons seemed to follow the work of an author named Mary C. Bartlett in particular, creating a scrapbook of articles/short stories by her. The articles mostly appeared in the Independant and the Christian Register from 1880-1915. The scrapbook had to be discarded due to mold and deterioration but a sample of the pages was kept.
The Huntingtons also saved a great number of programs from various musical and dramatic performances. Some of these programs include handwritten annotations of who actually attended each event. Many of the church programs may be from HSH's church. Some contain handwritten notes from HSH.
Several folders contain invitations and announcements of weddings, funerals, and births. The social custom of "calling cards" is well documented. Some of the cards are elaborately printed while others are handwritten. Some appear to have been used as place-cards at dinner tables. A number of greeting cards from various holidays and birthdays were also kept. Those sent to the Huntingtons were all saved -- though for their lack of content were not kept with the general correspondence. Still others were completely blank, as though being preserved for future use.
Arrangement
I. Family Correspondence, 1850-1947, n.d.
II. General Correspondence, 1857-1924, n.d.
III. Writings, 1851-1931, n.d.
IV. Biographical Documentation, 1849-1949, n.d.
V. Collected Material, 1827-1926, n.d.
Clergy; Missions -- Turkey; Huntington, Ellsworth, 1876-1947; Huntington, Henry Strong, 1836-1920
- Family Correspondence, 1850-1947, n.d.; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The Family correspondence is divided into five sub-series:
  Henry Strong Huntington to wife and children
  Mary Lawrence Herbert Huntington to husband and children
  Children and grandchildren of HSH and MLH
  HSH and MLH with their parents, siblings
  Extended family (cousins, aunts, uncles)
  HSH and MLH wrote joint letters to their children while traveling together in Europe during 1908-1909 and these letters appear in the first sub-series.
  - Henry Strong Huntington (HSH) to wife and children
    - HSH to Mary Lawrence Herbert (MLH), 1869-1870 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
    - HSH to Mary Lawrence (Herbert) Huntington, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - HSH to Family, 1873-1874 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - HSH to Family, 1875-1887 (Box 2, Folder 10-18)
    - HSH to Family, 1888-1907 (Box 3, Folder 19-27)
    - HSH/MLH to Family, 1908 Jan-Feb (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - HSH/MLH to Family, 1908 Mar-1909 (Box 4, Folder 29-33)
    - HSH to Family, 1910-1919, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 34-36)
    - HSH: Fragments, 1909, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Mary Lawrence Herbert (MLH) to husband and children
    - MLH to Henry Strong Huntington (HSH), 1864, 1869-1870 Aug (Box 4, Folder 38-41)
    - MLH to HSH, 1870 Sep-1887 (Box 5, Folder 42-50)
    - MLH to Family, 1888 -1893 Jun (Box 5, Folder 51-54)
    - MLH to Family ( For 1908-1909 see: folders 28-33), 1893 Jul-1920 (Box 6, Folder 55-66)
    - MLH to Family, 1921-1924, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 67-71)
    - MLH: Fragments, 1864, 1872, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Children and Grandchildren of HSH and MLH
    - Cornelia Huntington to Family, 1879-1892 (Box 7, Folder 73-79)
    - Cornelia to Family, 1893-1904 (Box 8, Folder 80-85)
    - Cornelia Huntington and Theron J. Damon to Family, 1908-1919 (Box 8, Folder 86-91)
    - Cornelia/Theron to Family, 1920-1939, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 92-100)
    - Cornelia: Fragments, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Non-Family to Cornelia, 1873-1921, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Theresa Huntington to Family, 1885-1906 (Box 9, Folder 103-106)
    - Zeigler, Charles and Theresa (Huntington), 1908-1923, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Theresa: Fragments, 1937, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Theresa/Charles to/from Non-Family, 1900-1909, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Ellsworth Huntington to Family, 1884-1908 (Box 9, Folder 110-113)
    - Huntington, Ellsworth and Rachel Slocum (Brewer) to Family, 1915-1947, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 114-117)
    - Ellsworth: Fragments, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Non-Family to Ellsworth, 1886-1921 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - George Huntington to Family, 1884-1902 (Box 10, Folder 120-131)
    - George to Family, 1903-1914 (Box 11, Folder 132-139)
    - Huntington, George and Elizabeth W. (Dodge) to Family, 1915-1921 (Box 11, Folder 140-144)
    - George/Elizabeth to Family, 1922-1942 (Box 12, Folder 145-153)
    - George: Fragments, 1900, 1902, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - Non-Family to George, 1886 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Henry Strong Huntington, Jr. (Harry) to Family, 1887-1909 (Box 12, Folder 156-162)
    - Harry to Family, 1910-1911 (Box 13, Folder 163)
    - Huntington, Henry Strong Jr. (Harry) and Edith Marguerita (Foster) to Family, 1912-1943, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 164-177)
    - Non-Family to Harry, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Ruth Lawrence Huntington to Family, 1887-1904 (Box 13, Folder 179-180)
    - Fletcher, Samuel A. (Sam) and Ruth L. (Huntington) to Family, 1905-1924, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 181-190)
    - Non-Family to Ruth, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Huntington Children to Family: Unidentified Fragments, 1886-1924, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Grandchildren to HSH/MLH, 1907-1944 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - HSH and MLH with their parents, siblings
    - Huntington, Henry S. and Mary L. to Parents (Oliver and Eunice Huntington and George and Theresa Herbert), 1853, 1855 (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1871-1880 (Box 14, Folder 194)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 195)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1882 Jan-Sep (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1882 Oct-Dec (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - MLH to Parents, 1883 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - MLH to Parents, 1884 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1885 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - MLH to Parents, 1886 Jan-Jun (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - MLH to Parents, 1886 Jul-Dec (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1887 Jan-Jun (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, 1887 Jul-Dec (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - MLH to Parents, 1888 Jan-Jun (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - MLH to Parents, 1888 Jul-Dec (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - MLH to Parents, 1889 Jan-Mar (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - MLH to Parents, 1889 Apr-Dec (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - HSH/MLH to Parents, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Huntington, Oliver Ellsworth and Eunice (Hitchcock) (OEH/EHH) to Henry Strong Huntington (HSH), 1852-1867 (Box 16, Folder 210-213)
    - OEH/EHH to HSH and Mary Lawrence Herbert, 1868-1872 (Box 16, Folder 214-220)
    - OEH/EHH to HSH/MLH, 1873-1880 (Box 17, Folder 221-226)
    - EHH to HSH/MLH, 1882-1910 (Box 17, Folder 227-233)
    - OEH/EHH to HSH/MLH, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - Non-Family to OEH, 1827-1841 (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - Non-Family to EHH, 1852-1878 (Box 18, Folder 236)
    - Herbert, George and Theresa (Arms) to Mary Lawrence Herbert, 1863-1866 (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - Herberts to MLH, 1867-1869 (Box 18, Folder 238-239)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH, 1870-1872 Jun (Box 18, Folder 240-244)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH, 1872 Jul-1879 Jul (Box 19, Folder 245-255)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH, 1879 Aug-1885 (Box 20, Folder 256-266)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH, 1886 -1892, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 267-276)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 277-278)
    - Herberts to HSH/MLH: Fragments, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 279)
    - Herberts to/from Non-Family, 1868-1890, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 280)
    - Gaytes, Carol and Theresa Herbert to HSH/MLH (sister of MLH), 1865-1881 (Box 22, Folder 281-289)
    - Gaytes to HSH/MLH, 1882-1890 (Box 23, Folder 290-299)
    - Gaytes to HSH/MLH, 1891-1905 (Box 24, Folder 300-308)
    - Gaytes to HSH/MLH, 1906-1923 (Box 25, Folder 309-319)
    - Gaytes to HSH/MLH, 1924, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 320-322)
    - Gaytes: Fragments, 1876, 1924, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 323)
    - Non-Family to Gaytes, 1891-1912 (Box 26, Folder 324)
  - Extended family
    - Extended Family to HSH/MLH, 1862-1875 (Box 26, Folder 325-333)
    - Extended Family to HSH/MLH, 1876-1913 (Box 27, Folder 334-344)
    - Extended Family to HSH/MLH, 1914-1924, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 345-346)
    - HSH to Extended Family, 1850, 1912 (Box 28, Folder 347)
    - MLH to Extended Family, 1850-1867, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 348)
    - Theresa Huntington to Extended Family, 1884, 1889, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 349)
    - EHH to Extended Family, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 350)
    - Herberts to Extended Family, 1865-1889, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 351)
    - Gaytes to Extended Family, 1881-1889, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 352)
    - Extended Family to Other Family, 1871-1938, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 353)
- General Correspondence, 1857-1924, n.d.; Series II
  The series is divided into two sub-series:
  Correspondence to/from Henry Strong Huntington
  Correspondence to/from Mary Lawrence Herbert Huntington
  - Correspondence to/from Henry Strong Huntington
    - A, 1890-1914, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 354)
    - Abbe, Julia A.J., 1907, 1916, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 355)
    - Alvord, Henry C., 1892-1918 (Box 28, Folder 355)
    - American Bible Society, 1885 (Box 28, Folder 356)
    - ABCFM, 1871, 1888 (Box 28, Folder 356)
    - American Missionary Association, 1896, 1906 (Box 28, Folder 356)
    - Arms, H.P., 1865-1872 (Box 28, Folder 357)
    - Ayer, F.D., 1869-1873 (Box 28, Folder 357)
    - Ba-Be, 1864-1913, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 358)
    - Bi-Bu, 1862-1916, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - Bacon, Edward E., 1884-1912, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - Baldwin, Gov. Simeon E., 1913 (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - Bard, G.I., 1870-1906, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 361)
    - Barnum, H.S., 1897, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - Bean, D.M., 1863-1871 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Bean, G.A., 1873-1892 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Bean, Harriet A., 1896-1914 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Beard, A.F., 1864-1917 (Box 29, Folder 364)
    - Bethany, NY Church Sunday School, 1892 (Box 29, Folder 365)
    - Brown, Robert, 1902-1911 (Box 29, Folder 366)
    - Browne, Rev. John K., 1900-1906 (Box 29, Folder 366)
    - Bruce, Henry J., 1869-1907 (Box 29, Folder 367)
    - Butler, F.E., 1857-1863, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 368)
    - Ca-Cl, 1861-1913, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 369)
    - Co-Cu, 1863-1911, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 370)
    - Carr, Daniel, 1868-1871, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - Caswell, Harriet, 1892-1907 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - Clark, [W.M.?], 1866-1878 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - Cousens, F.G., 1880-1904 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - Currier, A.H., 1864-1904 (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - D, 1864-1919, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 373)
    - Davis, L.K., 1864-1894, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - Davis, John, 1867-1897 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Davis, W.M., 1903-1907 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Duncan, Harriet E., 1872-1897, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - E, 1861-1915, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 377)
    - Eaton, J.M.R., 1864-1871 (Box 29, Folder 378)
    - Edwards, Alfred, 1870-1903 (Box 30, Folder 379)
    - Ellsworth, Oliver, 1864 (Box 30, Folder 380)
    - F, 1868-1915, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - Fairbank, Ida, 1906-1909 (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - Fletcher, Jennie C., 1904-1917 (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - Freeland, S.M., 1861-1907 (Box 30, Folder 383)
    - G, 1871-1911, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 384)
    - Galesburg, IL (First Church of Christ), 1892-1893 (Box 30, Folder 385)
    - Gates, Caleb F., 1900 (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - Giles, Madeline, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - Gorham, ME (First Congregational Church), 1877-1883 (Box 30, Folder 387)
    - Gulliver, John Putnam, 1871-1894 (Box 30, Folder 388)
    - Ha-He, 1865-1910, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 389)
    - Hi-Hy, 1864-1913, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 390)
    - Harriman, Frank, 1870-1873 (Box 30, Folder 391)
    - Harris, Amanda B., 1864-1916, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 392)
    - Harris, Mary Bartlett, 1864-1917, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 393)
    - Hamlin, Cyrus, 1890-1897 (Box 30, Folder 394)
    - Hubbel, James W., 1863-1888 (Box 30, Folder 395)
    - Huntington, 1868-1916 (Box 30, Folder 396)